// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q024: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Hillside Amusement Park is one of the most popular tourist ------ in the area and many people visit there.',
      choices: ['attracts', 'attractions', 'attractive', 'attractively'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['attractions'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'To ------ to our Budget Travel Magazine, you can sign up either by mail or on our website.',
      choices: ['promote', 'establish', 'prescribe', 'subscribe'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['subscribe'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Lucas Programing school offers a wide ------ of programming courses for beginners, including children.',
      choices: ['variety', 'varieties', 'vary', 'various'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['variety'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Cheng and Ms. Matsui were asked to ------ the cause of yesterday’s machine malfunction.',
      choices: ['accommodate', 'suspend', 'examine', 'decline'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['examine'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ hundreds of medical professionals at a convention in Seoul last week.',
      choices: ['A few', 'Some of the', 'Having had', 'There were'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['There were'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Lee’s extensive ------ and sufficient work experience make her the perfect candidate for the position.',
      choices: ['experts', 'expert', 'expertise', 'expertly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['expertise'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Please submit your summer vacation schedule by the end of this week ------ your preferred vacation dates can be approved.',
      choices: ['due to', 'so that', 'despite', 'therefore'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['so that'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The latest survey report indicates that demand for existing homes is a bit ------ than expected.',
      choices: ['lowest', 'lowing', 'low', 'lower'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['lower'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'As an apology for this delivery delay, we would like to ------ shipping charges for your next order.',
      choices: ['commend', 'implement', 'waive', 'postpone'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['waive'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Mr. Toyota in the public relations department has a wealth of ideas ------ a great ability to put them into action.',
      choices: ['in addition to', 'as long as', 'furthermore', 'because'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['in addition to'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}